We've made contact with a new alien species and apparently they're foodies. Oh
Foodies the worst. Mr. Ramsey will need you to cook for them
You'll have access to everything the area 51 test kitchen has to offer including top-secret alien cooking technology. Wait
That's just a hex clamp pan. I've got these at home
Unfortunately, it was leaked eight years ago. The pan was developed using material from an alien spacecraft
What?
Extremely durable, but low friction.
Created to deal with a thick egg-like atmosphere.
You're saying the pen I use to farm my bacon
is made out of flying saucers?
We don't have time for a science lesson, Mr. Ramsay.
The alien ambassador's already here.
Whoa.
Not her. Him.
Hey, what's up, dude?
You're an alien?
All famous people are aliens.
I'm not.
I meant, like, really famous people.
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Huh?