Right this second at some diner somewhere, I'll have uh, someone really wants a soda
And they're not alone because somewhere else there's a bunch of other someones that are also thinking about soda
like her
Hello, are you okay? I'm thinking see
The soda feels like a lot of sugar right now
And these other drinks too much buzz
No flavor. What if there were a better soda?
Hurry up!
Hey, yo!
Hunt!
Bestie!
Okay, I'm gonna freak out.
It's a drive-through, not a confession booth.
Show up a poppy, please.
Stop spiraling.
Get a poppy.
Don't mind if I do.
Pizza?
Hello, poppy.
Hey.
Oh, yes.
What a line-up.
Okay.
I mean, a soda with five grams of sugar?
It's good, right?
You